AFTER HE ANNOUNCED ON SOCIAL
MEDIA. HE WAS STEPPING DOWN
FROM
FROM OFFICE.
MEDIA. HE WAS STEPPING DOWN
FROM OFFICE. HE
FROM OFFICE. HE SET
MEDIA. HE WAS STEPPING DOWN
FROM OFFICE. HE SET TO
FROM OFFICE. HE SET TO BE
SENTENCED
SENTENCED JULY
FROM OFFICE. HE SET TO BE
SENTENCED JULY 21ST.
SENTENCED JULY 21ST. NEW
FROM OFFICE. HE SET TO BE
SENTENCED JULY 21ST. NEW AT
SENTENCED JULY 21ST. NEW AT 11
DROUGHT
DROUGHT CONDITIONS
SENTENCED JULY 21ST. NEW AT 11
DROUGHT CONDITIONS REMAIN
SEVERE
SEVERE TO
DROUGHT CONDITIONS REMAIN
SEVERE TO EXTREME
SEVERE TO EXTREME ACROSS
DROUGHT CONDITIONS REMAIN
SEVERE TO EXTREME ACROSS NORTH
FLORIDA
FLORIDA AND
SEVERE TO EXTREME ACROSS NORTH
FLORIDA AND SOUTH
FLORIDA AND SOUTH GEORGIA.
SEVERE TO EXTREME ACROSS NORTH
FLORIDA AND SOUTH GEORGIA. THE
NATIONAL
NATIONAL WEATHER
FLORIDA AND SOUTH GEORGIA. THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE SAYS
IT'S
IT'S THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE SAYS
IT'S THE WORST
IT'S THE WORST DROUGHT
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE SAYS
IT'S THE WORST DROUGHT ARE
AREA
AREA HAS
IT'S THE WORST DROUGHT ARE
AREA HAS SEEN
AREA HAS SEEN SINCE
IT'S THE WORST DROUGHT ARE
AREA HAS SEEN SINCE 2011
AREA HAS SEEN SINCE 2011 TODAY
OUR
OUR JULIA
AREA HAS SEEN SINCE 2011 TODAY
OUR JULIA MILLER
OUR JULIA MILLER TALKED
AREA HAS SEEN SINCE 2011 TODAY
OUR JULIA MILLER TALKED WITH
LOCAL
LOCAL FARMERS
OUR JULIA MILLER TALKED WITH
LOCAL FARMERS ABOUT
LOCAL FARMERS ABOUT HOW
OUR JULIA MILLER TALKED WITH
LOCAL FARMERS ABOUT HOW IT'S
IMPACTING
IMPACTING THEM.
>>
>> IT'S
IMPACTING THEM.
>> IT'S CITRUS
>> IT'S CITRUS GROWING
IMPACTING THEM.
>> IT'S CITRUS GROWING SEASON
RIGHT
RIGHT NOW
>> IT'S CITRUS GROWING SEASON
RIGHT NOW AND
RIGHT NOW AND IT'S
>> IT'S CITRUS GROWING SEASON
RIGHT NOW AND IT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT
RIGHT IN
RIGHT NOW AND IT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT IN THE
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
RIGHT NOW AND IT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
DROUGHT.
DROUGHT. I
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
DROUGHT. I SPOKE
DROUGHT. I SPOKE TO
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS
DROUGHT. I SPOKE TO FARMERS
DROUGHT. I SPOKE TO FARMERS AT
FLORIDA,
FLORIDA, GEORGIA,
DROUGHT. I SPOKE TO FARMERS AT
FLORIDA, GEORGIA, CITRUS
FLORIDA, GEORGIA, CITRUS TODAY
AND
AND THEY
FLORIDA, GEORGIA, CITRUS TODAY
AND THEY SAY
AND THEY SAY IT'S
FLORIDA, GEORGIA, CITRUS TODAY
AND THEY SAY IT'S DRIER
AND THEY SAY IT'S DRIER THAN
THEY'VE
THEY'VE EVER
AND THEY SAY IT'S DRIER THAN
THEY'VE EVER SEEN
THEY'VE EVER SEEN IT
AND THEY SAY IT'S DRIER THAN
THEY'VE EVER SEEN IT BEFORE.
>>
>> IT
THEY'VE EVER SEEN IT BEFORE.
>> IT IS
>> IT IS DRY.
>>
>> I'VE
>> IT IS DRY.
>> I'VE EVER
>> I'VE EVER SEEN
>> IT IS DRY.
>> I'VE EVER SEEN THAT
FLORIDA,
FLORIDA, GEORGIA
>> I'VE EVER SEEN THAT
FLORIDA, GEORGIA CITRUS
FLORIDA, GEORGIA CITRUS HAS
ABOUT
ABOUT 6,000
FLORIDA, GEORGIA CITRUS HAS
ABOUT 6,000 CITRUS
ABOUT 6,000 CITRUS TREES.
FLORIDA, GEORGIA CITRUS HAS
ABOUT 6,000 CITRUS TREES. AND
RIGHT
RIGHT NOW
ABOUT 6,000 CITRUS TREES. AND
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE IN
ABOUT 6,000 CITRUS TREES. AND
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE IN PRIME
GROWING
GROWING SEASON.
>>
>> THE
GROWING SEASON.
>> THE TREES
>> THE TREES ARE
GROWING SEASON.
>> THE TREES ARE JUST
>> THE TREES ARE JUST NOW
STARTING
STARTING TO
>> THE TREES ARE JUST NOW
STARTING TO PUT
STARTING TO PUT ON
>> THE TREES ARE JUST NOW
STARTING TO PUT ON BLUE
INVOLVED.
>>
>> MANAGER
INVOLVED.
>> MANAGER DALE
>> MANAGER DALE ALDRIDGE
INVOLVED.
>> MANAGER DALE ALDRIDGE SAYS
THE
THE DROUGHT
>> MANAGER DALE ALDRIDGE SAYS
THE DROUGHT IS
THE DROUGHT IS ALREADY
>> MANAGER DALE ALDRIDGE SAYS
THE DROUGHT IS ALREADY CAUSING
SOME
SOME CHALLENGES,
THE DROUGHT IS ALREADY CAUSING
SOME CHALLENGES, INCLUDING
HAVING
HAVING TO
SOME CHALLENGES, INCLUDING
HAVING TO USE
HAVING TO USE MORE
SOME CHALLENGES, INCLUDING
HAVING TO USE MORE WATER
HAVING TO USE MORE WATER THAN
NORMAL.
>>
>> BE
NORMAL.
>> BE MORE
>> BE MORE MORE
NORMAL.
>> BE MORE MORE MONEY
>> BE MORE MORE MONEY SPENT
NORMAL.
>> BE MORE MORE MONEY SPENT ON
POWER
POWER BILLS
>> BE MORE MORE MONEY SPENT ON
POWER BILLS BECAUSE
POWER BILLS BECAUSE THESE
WHALES,
WHALES, ONE-OFF
POWER BILLS BECAUSE THESE
WHALES, ONE-OFF ELECTRIC
MOTORS.
MOTORS. SO
WHALES, ONE-OFF ELECTRIC
MOTORS. SO WE'LL
MOTORS. SO WE'LL SEE
WHALES, ONE-OFF ELECTRIC
MOTORS. SO WE'LL SEE SOME
INCREASE
INCREASE IN
MOTORS. SO WE'LL SEE SOME
INCREASE IN THAT
INCREASE IN THAT BECAUSE
MOTORS. SO WE'LL SEE SOME
INCREASE IN THAT BECAUSE WE
HAVE
HAVE TO
INCREASE IN THAT BECAUSE WE
HAVE TO WATER
HAVE TO WATER MORE.
INCREASE IN THAT BECAUSE WE
HAVE TO WATER MORE. AND
THERE'S
THERE'S ALSO
HAVE TO WATER MORE. AND
THERE'S ALSO SOME
THERE'S ALSO SOME UNCERTAINTY
AS
AS THE
THERE'S ALSO SOME UNCERTAINTY
AS THE CITRUS
AS THE CITRUS CONTINUES
THERE'S ALSO SOME UNCERTAINTY
AS THE CITRUS CONTINUES TO
GROW
GROW DURING
AS THE CITRUS CONTINUES TO
GROW DURING THE
GROW DURING THE DROUGHT,
ALDRIDGE
ALDRIDGE SAYS
GROW DURING THE DROUGHT,
ALDRIDGE SAYS THEY
ALDRIDGE SAYS THEY WON'T
GROW DURING THE DROUGHT,
ALDRIDGE SAYS THEY WON'T KNOW
UNTIL
UNTIL LATER
ALDRIDGE SAYS THEY WON'T KNOW
UNTIL LATER IN
UNTIL LATER IN THE
ALDRIDGE SAYS THEY WON'T KNOW
UNTIL LATER IN THE SEASON.
WHAT
WHAT IMPACT
UNTIL LATER IN THE SEASON.
WHAT IMPACT IT
WHAT IMPACT IT COULD
UNTIL LATER IN THE SEASON.
WHAT IMPACT IT COULD HAVE
WHAT IMPACT IT COULD HAVE ON
THE
THE FRUIT.
WHAT IMPACT IT COULD HAVE ON
THE FRUIT. BUT
THE FRUIT. BUT NOW.
>>
>> BEING
THE FRUIT. BUT NOW.
>> BEING WE'RE
>> BEING WE'RE GOOD
THE FRUIT. BUT NOW.
>> BEING WE'RE GOOD SHAPE.
>> BEING WE'RE GOOD SHAPE. BUT
THAT
THAT COULD
>> BEING WE'RE GOOD SHAPE. BUT
THAT COULD CHANGE.
THAT COULD CHANGE. AMERICA
WILL
WILL GO
THAT COULD CHANGE. AMERICA
WILL GO DOWN.
WILL GO DOWN. COULD
THAT COULD CHANGE. AMERICA
WILL GO DOWN. COULD BE
DEVASTATING.
DEVASTATING. YOU
WILL GO DOWN. COULD BE
DEVASTATING. YOU KNOW,
DEVASTATING. YOU KNOW, IF
WILL GO DOWN. COULD BE
DEVASTATING. YOU KNOW, IF YOU
HAD
HAD TO
DEVASTATING. YOU KNOW, IF YOU
HAD TO HAVE
HAD TO HAVE A
DEVASTATING. YOU KNOW, IF YOU
HAD TO HAVE A PARTNER
HAD TO HAVE A PARTNER TO
DEVASTATING. YOU KNOW, IF YOU
HAD TO HAVE A PARTNER TO SHOOT
UP
UP A
HAD TO HAVE A PARTNER TO SHOOT
UP A FEW
UP A FEW 2
HAD TO HAVE A PARTNER TO SHOOT
UP A FEW 2 WEEKS
UP A FEW 2 WEEKS TO
HAD TO HAVE A PARTNER TO SHOOT
UP A FEW 2 WEEKS TO GET
UP A FEW 2 WEEKS TO GET IT.
THEN
THEN ADD
UP A FEW 2 WEEKS TO GET IT.
THEN ADD IN
THEN ADD IN THE
UP A FEW 2 WEEKS TO GET IT.
THEN ADD IN THE BEST
THEN ADD IN THE BEST SPOT.
>>
>> GROWING
THEN ADD IN THE BEST SPOT.
>> GROWING SEASON
>> GROWING SEASON HERE
THEN ADD IN THE BEST SPOT.
>> GROWING SEASON HERE LAST
FROM
FROM NOW